[
    {
      "category":"childhood",
      "type":"multiple",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"In which city was I born?",
      "correct_answer":"Birmingham",
      "incorrect_answers":[
        "Pensacola",
        "New York",
        "Atlanta"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category":"general trivia",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"Colter is an only child.",
      "correct_answer":"True",
      "incorrect_answers":[
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category":"general trivia",
      "type":"multiple",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"Which company do I currently work for?",
      "correct_answer":"Cint",
      "incorrect_answers":[
        "Lego",
        "Google",
        "Amazon"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category":"family history",
      "type":"multiple",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"In which state did my paternal grandfather run for governor in 1958?",
      "correct_answer":"Alabama",
      "incorrect_answers":[
        "Georgia",
        "Hawaii",
        "Minnesota"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category":"pets",
      "type":"text",
      "difficulty":"medium",
      "question":"What was the name of my longset living pet?",
      "correct_answer":"Riley"
    },
    {
      "category":"childhood",
      "type":"multiple",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"What was my favorite toy growing up?",
      "correct_answer":"Lego",
      "incorrect_answers":[
        "Playmobil",
        "Barbie",
        "Hot Wheels"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category":"adulthood",
      "type":"multiple",
      "difficulty":"hard",
      "question":"What is my favorite foreign city?",
      "correct_answer":"Edinburgh",
      "incorrect_answers":[
        "Paris",
        "London",
        "Montreal"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category":"adulthood",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"Colter once took a two week trip to China.",
      "correct_answer":"False",
      "incorrect_answers":[
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category":"college",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"medium",
      "question":"Colter has a degree in Computer Science.",
      "correct_answer":"False",
      "incorrect_answers":[
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category":"childhood",
      "type":"multiple",
      "difficulty":"hard",
      "question":"Who was Colter's best friend in 4th grade?",
      "correct_answer":"Karl Antonucci",
      "incorrect_answers":[
        "Marcus Tortorici",
        "Damon Belton",
        "Maxwell Korn"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category":"family history",
      "type":"multiple",
      "difficulty":"medium",
      "question":"My maternal grandfather played college football for which school?",
      "correct_answer":"Baylor University",
      "incorrect_answers":[
        "Auburn University",
        "The Universtiy of Alabama",
        "The University of Georgia"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category":"adulthood",
      "type":"multiple",
      "difficulty":"medium",
      "question":"Which coding bootcamp did Colter attend?",
      "correct_answer":"Flatiron School",
      "incorrect_answers":[
        "Columbia Engineering Bootcamp",
        "The Universtiy of Alabama",
        "Fullstack Academy"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category":"family history",
      "type":"text",
      "difficulty":"hard",
      "question":"What state and/or colony did the Longshore family first emigrate to?",
      "correct_answer":"Pennsylvania"
    },
    {
      "category":"general triva",
      "type":"boolean",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"Colter loves building Lego.",
      "correct_answer":"True",
      "incorrect_answers":[
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category":"pets",
      "type":"multiple",
      "difficulty":"hard",
      "question":"How many pets has Colter had in his life?",
      "correct_answer":"14",
      "incorrect_answers":[
        "7",
        "12",
        "11"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category":"adulthood",
      "type":"multiple",
      "difficulty":"easy",
      "question":"Which gym franchise did Colter work for?",
      "correct_answer":"Iron Tribe Fitness",
      "incorrect_answers":[
        "Orange Theory Fitness",
        "The YMCA",
        "Gold's Gym"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category":"family history",
      "type":"multiple",
      "difficulty":"medium",
      "question":"Colter's paternal great-grandfather played college baseball for which school?",
      "correct_answer":"The University of Alabama",
      "incorrect_answers":[
        "Vanderbilt University",
        "Tulane University",
        "Samford University"
      ]
    }
]
